Button, Daniel Evan; Papers apap231
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Daniel Evan Button Papers
1962-1971
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Button, Daniel E. (Daniel Evan), 1917-2009
apap231
42.2 cubic ft.
The Daniel Evan Button Papers contain Button’s records of his terms as a U.S. Representative of the 29th Congressional District of New York.
Access
Access to the collection is unrestricted with the exception of one folder in series 2 and several individual folders in series 5 because of the large amount of personal records (medical and educational) contained in the files.
Acquisition Information
Daniel Button initially donated his papers to Syracuse University. In 2006, the papers were transferred to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Biographical History
Daniel Evan Button was a U.S. Representative from New York. Button was born in Dunkirk, Chautauqua County, NY on November 1, 1917. He graduated from Wilmington High School (Delaware) in 1933, received his A.B. from the University of Delaware (Newark, DE) in 1938, and his M.A. from Columbia University in 1939. Button was an author and journalist who worked at newspapers in Wilmington, with the Associated Press in New York City (1939-1947) and as executive editor of the Albany Times-Union (1960-1966). He served as the assistant to the president of the State University of New York (1952-1958) as well as on the staffs of the University of Delaware and Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute.
Button was elected in 1966 as a Republican in the 29th district, which includes Albany and Schenectady counties, as well as part of Rensselaer County. At this time, the 29th district’s population was approximately 462,338 citizens. Button was part of the 90th and the subsequent Congress (January 3, 1967-January 3, 1971), but was an unsuccessful candidate for reelection in 1970. While serving as a U.S. Representative, Button was on the Merchant Marine and Fisheries, and Post Office and Civil Services Committees. While in office, he was critical of the war in Vietnam.
Button wrote two books, Lindsay, A Man for Tomorrow (1965) and Take City Hall (2003). He also was editor for Science Digest from 1976 to 1980.
Button was the president of the board of directors of the Clinton Square Neighborhood House and Citizens Committee for Albany Public Schools as well as for the Arthritis Foundation (1971-1975). He was director of the Council of Community Services, a trustee of the Mohawk-Hudson Council on Educational Television, and active on the boards of the World Affairs Council, as well as the American Association for the United Nations, Albany Fair Housing Committee, the Albany YWCA, and Citizens Planning Committee. In addition, Button was co-moderator for the television program, “Speak for Yourself.”
Button died of pneumonia on May 7, 2009 at age 91 and is buried in Albany Rural Cemetery in Menands, New York.
Scope and Contents
This collection documents the political life of Daniel Evan Button. This collection represents Button’s administrative actions during his two terms as a U.S. Representative: his contributions to legislation, files he received concerning domestic concerns and foreign relations, a sizable amount of correspondence he received from Albany residents, military case files for every military branch, as well as press releases and teleprompter papers for televised events.
Button served on the Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee as well as the Post Office and Civil Services Commission. Materials related to these assignments are dispersed throughout the collection, primarily in subject files and subject correspondence. Button also sponsored several bills pertaining to these two committees.
While in office, Joseph or “Joe” Parillo was Button’s personal assistant in his Schenectady office. Also, Button had at least two secretaries who assisted him with his correspondence and case files. There are a number of records that contain notes regarding cases from these personnel.
Please note there is no material concerning Button’s two books in this collection. There is also no material about his work at Times-Union, University at Albany, or his contributions to different societies. The entirety of this collection is from his time as U.S. Representative.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1 - HR, Legislation and Bills, 1964-1971, Undated
Series 2 - Subject Files, 1962-1971, Undated
Series 3 - Subject Correspondence, 1966-1970, Undated
Series 4 - Correspondence, 1967-1970
Series 5 - Case Files, 1965-1971, Undated
Series 6 - Communication, 1965-1970, Undated
Series 1, 2, 3, and 6 are arranged alphabetically. Series 4 and 5 are arranged chronologically.
Schenectady, New York; Public Servants; Politics and Politicians; Military and Armed Conflict; Albany, New York; Postal service censorship; Veterans--Medical Care--United States; Veterans--Employment--United States; Military discharge--United States.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975--Public opinion.; Complaints (Military law); New York (State)--Politics and government; Albany (N.Y.); Washington (D.C.); Bills (legislative records); Legislative Records; Files by subject; Correspondence; Press Releases; Clippings; Photographs; Speeches; Button, Daniel E. (Daniel Evan), 1917-2009; United States. Congress. House.; United States. Congress. House. Committee on Merchant Marine and Fisheries; United States. Congress. House. Committee on Post Office and Civil Service
- HR, Legislation and Bills, 1964-1971; Undated; 1; 4.8 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically and by HR number.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains material on bills that Daniel Button sponsored and/or voted for, including vote tallies and statements of his support in Congressional records. Many of these bills are attached to supplemental materials such as correspondence.
  - H.R. 8 prohibit relief supplies, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 1)
  - H.R. 17 to create select committee to conduct an investigation and study of crime in the United States [roll call 53] [Button sponsored identical H.R. 33], 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 2)
  - H.Con.Res. 20 Joint Committee on Crime, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 3)
  - H.R. 21 investigative authority, committee on interior and insular affairs, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 4)
  - H.R. 47 Family Moving Tax, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 5)
  - H.J.Res. 54 conservative of natural resources, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 6)
  - H.J.Res. 56 joint crime committee, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 7)
  - H.R. 47 investigate authority committee on veterans affairs, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 8)
  - H.R. 56 lower voting age to 18, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 9)
  - H.R. 66 small business investigations, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 10)
  - H.R. 76 investigative authority committee on the District of Columbia, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 11)
  - H.R. 89 to change the name of the committee on Un-American Activities to Committee on Internal Security, roll call 16, 17, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 12)
  - H.R. 93 investigative authority committee on the judiciary, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 13)
  - H.R. 96 relief to persons affected by Nigerian civil war, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 14)
  - H.R. 105 investigative authority committee on armed services, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 15)
  - A.R.116 investigative authority committee on interstate and foreign committee, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 16)
  - H.R. 120 and 121, urban affairs, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 17)
  - H.R. 156 arms race in the Middle East, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 18)
  - H.R. 157 commission for economic development of the Middle East, 1969; Undated (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 19)
  - H.R. 173 return from Peru of U.S. destroyer, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 20)
  - H.R. 176 congressman for District of Columbia, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 21)
  - H.R. R.177 United Nations, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 22)
  - H.R. 184 select committee to study urban area problems, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 23)
  - H.R. 219 to encourage gerontology, 1969; Undated (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 24)
  - H.R. 223 and 349 select committee on standards and conduct, 1967; Undated (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 25)
  - H.Res. 229 all-volunteer military (draft), 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 26)
  - H.R. 247 national park system, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 27)
  - H.J.R. 254 violence on TV, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 28)
  - H.R. 254 to authorize the expansion of the DC police canine corps [passed voice], 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 29)
  - H.R. 255 installment loan interest in DC [ roll call 255], 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 30)
  - H.Con.R. 261 Peru and U.S. vessels, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 31)
  - H.J.R. 264 proposing an amendment to constitution relative to equal rights for men and women [passed roll call 262 and 263], 1969-1970; Undated (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 32)
  - H.R. 270 authorizing expenditure of funds for expenses of the committee on internal security, roll call 33234 - includes vote, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 33)
  - H.R. 272 interns, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 34)
  - H.R. 273 to amend X, XI and XIII, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 35)
  - H.R. 279 newspaper preservation act [passed roll call 206], 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 36)
  - H.Con.R. 284 Atlantic Union, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 37)
  - H.R. 297 Federal Education Programs, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 38)
  - H.R. 306 to create a delegation to a convention of North Atlantic Nations, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 39)
  - H.R. 315 to establish a joint committee on foreign information and intelligence, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 40)
  - H.R. 330 and 331 right to vote at 18, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 41)
  - H.R. 349 committee on rules, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 42)
  - H.R. 357 additional clerk [roll call 91] includes vote, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 43)
  - H.Con.R. 360 North Vietnam and the National Liberation Front of South Vietnam, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 44)
  - H.R. 378 select committee on Congressional mailing standards, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 45)
  - H.Con.Res. 403 to withdraw all United States forces from Vietnam, 1969; Undated (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 46)
  - H.Res. 416 student interns introduced, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 47)
  - H.R. 426 military forces in Congo, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 48)
  - H.Con.R. 428 to terminate the authority of the Gulf of Tonkin joint resolution, 1964; 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 49)
  - H.R. 439 resubmit Geneva Protocol 1925, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 50)
  - H.R. 452 urge the Soviet Union to process requests for reunions, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 51)
  - H.Con.R. 462 stereotyped-films and broadcasts, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 52)
  - H.J.R. 468 "Rush - Bagot Agreement Days", 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 53)
  - H.R. 468 seeking arms limitation with the Soviet Union, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 54)
  - H.J.R. 483 Mid-Atlantic States Air Pollution Control Commission, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 55)
  - H.R. 497 to amend section 301 of manpower development and training act of 1962, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 56)
  - H.Con.R.511 selling Israel aircrafts for its defense, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 57)
  - H.R. 512 to creat select committee to conduct investigation of crime and disorder, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 58)
  - H.R. 514 to create committee to investigate crime on military installations, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 59)
  - H.R. 514 elementary and secondary education act of 1965 amendment, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 60)
  - H.R. 515 to amend the national school lunch act and the child nutrition act of 1966, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 61)
  - H.R. 530 condemn discrimination of catholic majority in northern Ireland, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 62)
  - H.Con.R. 531 establishing Congressional committee on foreign policy, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 63)
  - H.Con.R. 543, establish all-volunteer armed forces, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 64)
  - H.Con.R. 547 stop armed attacks on aircraft and passengers engaged in international travel, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 65)
  - H.R. 550 to create a committee to study the relocation of the naval-applied science laboratory, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 66)
  - H.R. 560 "National School Safety Patrol Week", 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 67)
  - H.R. 564 reduction of troops in Vietnam, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 68)
  - H.Con.Res. 579 interest rate policy, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 69)
  - H.R. 610 permanent peace in the Middle East, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 70)
  - H.R. 613 towards peace and justice in Vietnam [Roll call 294, 295], 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 71)
  - H.Con.R. 625 Kent State, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 72)
  - H.Con.R. 639 UN supervisory force to establish cease fire in Indochina, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 73)
  - H.J.R. 656 World Food Study Commission, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 74)
  - H.R. 656 to enter the Mid-Atlantic Atates Air Pollution Control Compact, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 75)
  - H.R. 661 commending the American service man and veteran of Vietnam for his efforts and sacrifice, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 76)
  - H.R. 675 to provide an extension for the interest equalization tax, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 77)
  - H.R. 668 world food study, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 78)
  - H.R. 670 To amend section 19(2) of the DC police assistance act of 1962, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 79)
  - H.R. 678 towards peace with justice in Vietnam, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 80)
  - N.J.Res. 681 presidential and vice presidential election [Roll call 177], 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 81)
  - H.R. 684 to make certain technical corrections in title 38, U.S code, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 82)
  - H.Con. R685 treatement and exchange of military and civilian prisoners in Vietnam, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 83)
  - H.R. 687 district constituting seat of government, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 84)
  - Legis.Con.Res. 690 United Nations (permanent UN peace - keeping force), 1966-1967; Undated (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 85)
  - H.R. 693 veterans and hospital expenses [Roll call 73] - includes vote, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 86)
  - H.Con.R. 693 International Environment Agency, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 87)
  - H.Con.R. 703 troop withdrawals, national policy, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 88)
  - H.Con.R. 715 joint-intelligence committee, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 89)
  - H.R. 734 creating a committee to investigate crime, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 90)
  - H.R. 735 to review military aid program, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 91)
  - S.742 Kennewick division extension, Yakima Project, Washington, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 92)
  - H.R. 758 committee on the environment, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 93)
  - H.R. 763 study of state laws governing youth camps [Roll call 72] - includes vote, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 94)
  - H.Res.768 Rhodesia sanction solution, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 95)
  - H.R. 770 civil service retirement, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 96)
  - H.J.Res. 794 proposing a constitutional amendment for equal rights for women and men, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 97)
  - H.R. 796 amending the rules of the House of Representatives, financial disclosure, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 98)
  - H.R. 833 to create a select committee to investigate riots, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 99)
  - H.R. 851 effects of federal policies on the quality of education in the US, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 100)
  - H.R. 860 employer contributins for joint industry promotion of products [Roll call 5], 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 101)
  - H.R. 882 restricting Governor Maddox as a guest in The House dining room, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 102)
  - H.R. 898 world habeas corpus, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 103)
  - H.R. 931 cabinet task force on oil import control, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 104)
  - H.R. 934 strategic arms limitations talks, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 105)
  - H.J.Res. 945 "National Blood Donor Month", 1969-1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 106)
  - H.J.Res. 955, appropriations for 1970 fiscal year, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 107)
  - H.R. 960 disapproving reorganization plan [defeated Roll call No.II 118], 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 108)
  - H.R. 962 military action involving US in Cambodia, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 109)
  - H.J.R. 966 appropriation for education, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 110)
  - H.R. 976 Southeast Asia [passed roll call 155,156,157], 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 111)
  - H.R. 985 expediture limitation on the American military effort in Southeast Asia, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 112)
  - H.Res. 1013 Ethics, select community standards and conduct, Mr. Bennett, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 113)
  - H.R. 1035 to ban sit-ins, camp-ins and sleep-ins in the Capital [roll call 80], 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 114)
  - S. 1058 to extend the period within which the [resident may transmit to Congress plans for reorganization of agencies of the Executive Branch, roll call 23 - vote, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 115)
  - H.R. 1069 three mile limit established on US coastline, 1968 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 116)
  - H.R. 1075 council on environmental quality [passed non-record vote], 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 117)
  - S. 1081 medals to honor dedication of the Winston Churchill Memorial and Library, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 118)
  - H.R. 1086 national commitment to control and cure cancer, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 119)
  - H.R. 1102 presidents veto of Hill-Button hospital constitution [passed, roll call 188], 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 120)
  - H.R. 1112 railway dispute [passed roll call 40], 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 121)
  - H.J.Res.1121 joint committee on environment and technology, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 122)
  - H.J.Res.1176 National Volunteer Firemen's Week, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 123)
  - H.R. 1191 and 5980, servicemen and their families - includes newsclippings, 1967; Undated (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 124)
  - H.J.Res.1194 "National Machine Tool Week", 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 125)
  - H.J.Res. 1215 representation of the District of Columbia in Congress, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 126)
  - H.J.Res. 1237 joint committee on peace, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 127)
  - H.J.Res. 1305 waterfront commission compact, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 128)
  - H.J.Res. 1349 feasibility of government acquisitions operation and maintenance of railroad tracks, rights of way, signal systems, and often fixed facilities, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 129)
  - H.R. 1400 military procurement authorization [roll calls 195,198,199,and 200], 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 130-131)
  - H.R. 1455 College Housing Loan Act, 1967 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 132)
  - S. 1458 prohibiting the bussiness of debt adjusting, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 133)
  - H.R. 1483 to resistrict travel in violation of area restrictions, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 134)
  - H.R. 1684 [passing roll calls 70-71], 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 135)
  - H.R. 1737 extending funding assistance for public broadcasing [roll call 215], 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 136)
  - H.R. 1857 public works and atomic energy commission appropriations bills [passed nonrecord vote], 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 137)
  - H.R. 2076 witholding of city incoming taxes on federal employees [passed, roll call 252], 1969-1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 138)
  - H.R. 2153 illegal transportation of cigarettes, includes background material, 1967; Undated (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 139)
  - H.R. 2171 relating to national observances and holidays, 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 140)
  - H.R. 2214 potato bill [passed voice vote], 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 141)
  - S. 2315 to restore the golden eagle program to the Land and Water Conservative Fund Act, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 142)
  - S. 2484 to authorize marketing agreememts for agreement for papayas, 1970 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 143)
  - H.R. 2777 Potato Research and Promotion Act [Roll call 267], 1969 (Box 1 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 144)
  - H.R. 2910 to authorize additional funds for the Library of Congress [passed roll call 42,43,44], 1970 (Box 2 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 1)
  - H.R. 3265 WOLD, sacred heart, relief of Sister Machi Shigehism and Sister Tamikoltitomi, 1965 (Box 2 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 2)
  - H.R. 3662, Sister Lourdes Buessa Oliver, Sister Matilde Gonzalez-Garcia, 1965 (Box 2 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 3)
  - H.R. 3689 concurrent jurisduction with the U.S. over the Veterans Administration Center, Fort Harrison, Montana, 1969 (Box 2 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 4)
  - H.R. 3786 Point Reyes National Seashore [Passed voice vote], 1969 (Box 2 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 5)